{
    "subject": "resource/The_Prometheus_Deception",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "The Prometheus Deception",
    "human_readable": "The label of The Prometheus Deception is 'The Prometheus Deception'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9708546996116638,
            "question": "What is the label of 'The Prometheus Deception'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.911249577999115,
            "question": "What information does the label 'The Prometheus Deception' provide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8891632556915283,
            "question": "Is there any other information about 'The Prometheus Deception' besides its label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8291435837745667,
            "question": "What kind of work is 'The Prometheus Deception'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7990695238113403,
            "question": "Is 'The Prometheus Deception' a book title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7582842707633972,
            "question": "What are some common themes or plot elements in works titled 'The Prometheus Deception'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7447200417518616,
            "question": "Does 'The Prometheus Deception' have a specific genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5761643648147583,
            "question": "Could 'The Prometheus Deception' be a movie or TV show title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5644586682319641,
            "question": "Would you be interested in learning more about 'The Prometheus Deception'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.01933131366968155,
            "question": "Can you think of other works with similar titles?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of The Prometheus Deception is 'The Prometheus Deception'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7235_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would you be interested in learning more about 'The Prometheus Deception'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7235_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could 'The Prometheus Deception' be a movie or TV show title?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7235_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does 'The Prometheus Deception' have a specific genre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7235_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7235_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7235_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7235_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7235_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7235_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7235_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7235_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7235_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7235_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7235_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe information in the documents does not mention that the label of \"The Prometheus Deception\" is indeed \"The Prometheus Deception\". In fact, it only talks about the book itself and its author Robert Ludlum. There is no indication that the title is a triple or a statement to be evaluated. Therefore, the correct answer is \"no\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The label \"The Prometheus Deception\" is actually a book title and not the book itself, being listed under \"Other authors\", \"Series and work relationships\", and as a book description, it's implying that this is an actual fact about the book, which is incorrect.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}